

# **Enmanuel Martínez Antigua**

Full Stack Web Developer

## Profile

I am a self-taught web developer, with more than 6 years of experience developing websites, web applications, administrative systems, and hybrid mobile applications. I describe myself as a person who likes to be updated with the new web standards and best practices.

# Employment History

#### Freelancer

2021-2023

- Creating Web Application for medical industry.
- Creating Websites for Non Profit and Physicians
- Building relationships with clients.
- Managing client relationships.

#### Bits & Bytes Media

2018-2020

- Working as Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Building with as a Lead developer an electoral roll aplication with PHP, MySQL, HTML5/CSS3 and
- Building variety of websites with CMS Software.
- Building a ERP for ecommerse sites, law firms, dealers.

#### Media Revolution

2017-mar. to 2017-nov.

- · Working as Front-End Web Developer.
- Building a mobile application with Ionic.
- Building a CRM for the mobile application with Angular.
- Working with a team of developer.

#### **Berry Dominicana**

2013-2015

• Service Order Keyer.

# Education

Psychology, Universidad Católica de Sando Domingo

2014-2017

Graduated with Honor

## Courses

JavaScript: Understanding the Weird Parts at Udemi. Certificate

Imparted by Anthony Alicea

Vue.js The complete guide at Udemi. Certificate

Imparted by Maximilian Schwarzmüller

Angular The Complete Guide at Udemi. Certificate

Imparted by Maximilian Schwarzmüller

Illustrator CC MasterClass at Udemi. Certificate

Imparted by Martin Perhiniak

Photoshop The Platform's Biggest & Most Popular Photoshop Course at Udemi. Certificate Imparted by Manfred Werner

Conversation and gramatic in English at Dominico Americano. Certificate

#### **Details**

Santo Domingo Dominican Republic 809-399-9429 enmanuelpsy@gmail.com

Instagram Portfolio Github

Reading, Dancing, Video Games, Exercises, Sports

#### **Programing Languages**

Javascript	
SQL	
Python	
PHP	

PHP	
<b>Front-End</b> React.js	
Vue.js	
Angular	
Next.js	
Typescript	
Vite	
Tailwind CSS	

Back-End Nodejs
Express.js
MySQL
PostgreSQL
Babel
Linux
Nginx
Apache

#### Design

2 00.g.i		
Illustrator		
Photoshop		

#### Coftware Davalanment Principles

Software Development Principles			
Clean Code			
Keep It Simple			
Don't repeat yourself			

#### Languages Spanich

Spanisn			
English			